<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pro At Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_inicio_cliente">inicioCliente</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Configuración</string>

    <string name="menu_editarPerfil">Perfil</string>
    <string name="menu_sesiones">Sesiones</string>
    <string name="menu_otros">Otros</string>
    <string name="menu_cerrarSesion">Cerrar Sesión</string>
    <string name="menu_inicio">Inicio</string>
    <string name="menu_privacidad">Politica de Privacidad</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scroll">ScrollActivity</string>

    <!--Aviso de privacidad-->
    <string name="p1_priv">De Conformidad con lo establecido en la Ley Federal de Protección de
        Datos Personales en Posesion de los Particulares, <b>PRO AT HOME.</b> pone a su
        disposicion el siguiente aviso de privacidad:\n\n<b>PRO AT HOME</b>, es responsable de uso y proteccion de sus datos
        personales, en este sentido y atendiendio las obligacviones legales establecidas
        en la Ley Federal de Protección de Datos Personales en Posesion de los
        Particulares, a traves de este instrumento se informa a los titulares de los datos, la
        informacion que de ellos se recaba y los fines que se le darán a dicha información.\n\nAdemás de lo anterior
        informamos que PRO AT HOME, tiene su domicilio en: \n\n
        <b>“CALLE DR. JOSE MARÍA VERTIZ NÚMERO 148 INTERIOR 4 COLONIA DOCTORES, ALCALDIA CUAUHTEMOC, CIUDAD DE MÉXICO.”</b>\n\nLos datos
        personales que recabamos de ustéd serán utilizados para las siguientes finalidades, las cuales son necesarias
        para concretar nuestra relacion con usted, asi como atender los servicios y/o pedidos que solicita, siendo estos:\n\n
        “EL APOYO PARA LA CAPACITACION PROFESIONAL Y ESPECIALIZADA EN EL IDIOMA INLGES, PARA QUE NUESTROS CLIENTES
        TENGAN LA MEJOR PREPARACIÓN POSIBLE Y LOGREN SU CERTIFICACION”\n\nPara llevar a cabo las finalidades descritas en el presente aviso de
        privacidad, utilizaremos los siguientes datos personales:\n\n<b>Nombre completo</b>\n<b>Edad</b>\n<b>Nacionalidad</b>\n<b>Domicilio
            actual</b>\n<b>Estado Civil</b>\n<b>Último grado de estudios</b>\n<b>Empleo o Profesión</b>\n<b>Numeros telefonicos: Fijo,
            Celular Oficina.</b>\n<b>Correo electrónico</b>\n<b>Redes Sociales: Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, WhatsApp, Snapchat.</b>\n\nPor otra parte,
        informamos que sus datos personales no serán compartidos con ninguna autoridad, empresa, organización o personas distinatas a nosotros
        y serán utilizados exclusivamenre para los fines señalados.\n\nUsted tiene en todo momento el derecho a conocer qyue datos personales poseemos,
        para que los utilizaremos y las condicines del uso que les damos (acceso). Asi mismo, es su derecho solicitar la corrección de su información
        personal en caso de que esta esté desactuializada, sea inexacta o incompleta; de igual manera, tiene derecho a que su informacion se elimine
        de nuestros reguistros o base de datos cuadno considere que la misma no esta siendo utilizada adecuadamente, así como tambien a oponerse al
        uso de sus datos personales patra fines específicos. Estos derechos se conocen como Derechos ARCO.\n\nPara el ejercicio de cualquiera de los
        Derechos ARCO, se deberá presentar la solicitud a través de los formatos que estarán a su disposición en:\n\n<b>“CALLE DR. JOSE MARÍA VERTIZ
            NÚMERO 148 INTERIOR 4 COLONIA DOCTORES, ALCALDIA CUAUHTEMOC, CIUDAD DE MÉXICO.”</b>\n\nLo anterior también servirá para conocer el procedimiento
        y requisitos para el ejercicio de los Derechos ARCO.\n\nLa respuesta a dicha solicitud se dará en 20 días hábiles y se le comunicara vía telefónica
        o por el correo electrónico proporcionado por el usuario.\n\nLos datos de contacto de la persona o departamento de datos personales, que está
        a cargo dar trámite a las solicitudes de Derechos ARCO es:\n\n<b>José Eduardo Herrera Leguizamo en el domicilio ubicado en “Calle Dr. José María Vertiz
            Número 148 interior 4, Colonia Doctores, Alcaldia Cuauhtemoc, Ciudad de México” con el numero de telefono 5572590933 y
            con el correo electronico anglit_cert@outlook.com </b>\n\nCabe mencionar que en cualquier momento usted puede revocar su concentimiento
        para el uso de sus datos personales. Del mismo modo, usted puede revocar el consentimiento que, en su caso, nos haya otorgado
        para el tratamiento de sus datos personales.\n\nAsí mismo, usted deberá considerar que para ciertos fines, la revocacion de su consentimiento
        implicara que no podamos seguir pretando el servicio que nos solicito, o la conclusión de su relacion con nostros.\n\nPara revocar el consentimiento
        que usted otroga en este acto o para limitar su divulgación, se deberá ´presentar la solicitud respectiva a través de los formatos que estarán
        a su disposicón en:\n\n<b>“CALLE DR. JOSE MARÍA VERTIZ NÚMERO 148 INTERIOR 4 COLONIA DOCTORES, ALCALDIA CUAUHTEMOC, CIUDAD DE MÉXICO.”</b>\n\nDel mismo modo,
        podrá solicitar la información para conocer el procedimiento y requisitos para la revocación del consentimiento, asi como limitar le uso
        y divulgación de su informaqcion personal.\n\nEn cualquier caso, la respuesta a las peticiones se dará a conocer en un plazo de 20 días hábiles.\n\nPor ultimo <b>PRO AT HOME</b>,
        se compromete a mantenerlo informado sobre cualquier cambio en nuestro modelo de trabajo o alguna otra modificacion de el giro social de esta,
        ya sea por disolicion fusión o modificación de denominación sociul, por lo cual nos comprometemos a mantenerlo informado sobre los cambios
        que pueda sufrir el presente aviso de provacidad, sin embargo, usted puiede solciatr informacion sobre si el mismo ha sufrido algún cambio
        a traves del siguiente correo electronico: anglit_cert@outlook.com\n\nAtentamente\n\n<b>PRO AT HOME</b>
    </string>


    <string name="large_text">

        <string name="card_chip_demo">Chip</string>
    <string name="card_message_demo_large">This is a secondary text for a card with three lines in the message.
        We can show more details about topic like specs.</string>
    <string name="card_message_demo_small">This is a secondary text for a card with two lines in the message.</string>
    <string name="card_secondary_demo">Secondary text</string>
    <string name="card_subtitle_demo">This is a subtitle</string>
    <string name="card_title_demo">This is a title</string>

    <string name="dialog_cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="dialog_chooser">Elegir</string>
    <string name="dialog_confirm">Confirmar</string>
    <string name="dialog_confirm_title">¿Confirmar acción?</string>
    <string name="dialog_full_screen">Pantalla completa</string>
    <string name="dialog_info">Informativo</string>
    <string name="dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="dialog_save">Save</string>

    <string name="error_price_min">El valor debe ser mayor o igual a 5.</string>

    <string name="helper_comment_optional">Comentario(opcional)</string>
    <string name="hint_capital_letter">Mayusculas</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>

    <string name="menu_favorites">Favoritos</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Perfil</string>
    <string name="menu_start">Inicio</string>

    <string name="message_action_success">Evento ocurrió exitosamente!</string>

    <string name="status_enabled">Enabled</string>
    <string name="status_custom">Personalizado</string>
    <string name="status_default">Default</string>
    <string name="status_disabled_indeterminate">Not Indeterminate</string>
    <string name="status_disabled_selected">Disabled Selected</string>
    <string name="status_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="status_enabled_indeterminate">Enabled Indeterminate</string>
    <string name="status_filled_dense">Filled Dense</string>
    <string name="status_icon_enabled">Icon</string>
    <string name="status_icon_text_enabled">Icon Text</string>
    <string name="status_legacy_style">Legacy Material Style</string>
    <string name="status_outlined_dense_enabled">Outlined Dense</string>
    <string name="status_outlined_enabled">Outlined</string>
    <string name="status_text_enabled">Text</string>
    <string name="status_unelevated_enabled">Unelevated enabled</string>

    <string name="title_activity_full">FullActivity</string>

    <string name="title_activity_static">StaticActivity</string>

        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Valores de la Sesión.</string>
    <string name="status_enabled">Enabled</string>
    <string name="status_disabled">Disabled</string>
    <string name="status_unelevated_enabled">Unelevated Enabled</string>
    <string name="status_outlined_enabled">Outlined</string>
    <string name="status_text_enabled">Text</string>
    <string name="status_icon_enabled">icon</string>
    <string name="status_custom">Personalizado</string>
    <string name="menu_ruta">Ruta de Aprendizaje</string>
    <string name="fecha_nacimiento">Fecha</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps_fragment">Map</string>
    <string name="menu_start">Nueva Sesión</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Gestionar Sesiones</string>
    <string name="direccion">Dirección:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_inicio_profesional">inicioProfesional</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="menu_material">Material</string>
    <string name="cambiar_foto">Cambiar foto</string>
    <string name="profesional_asignado">Profesional Asignado</string>
    <string name="horario">Horario</string>
    <string name="lugar">lugar (Dirección)</string>
    <string name="tiempo">Tiempo</string>
    <string name="nivel">Nivel</string>
    <string name="tipo">Tipo de Servicio</string>
    <string name="observaciones">Observaciones</string>
    <string name="solicitar">Solicitar</string>
    <string name="actualizar">Actualizar</string>
    <string name="eliminar">Eliminar</string>
    <string name="menu_ayuda">Ayuda</string>
    <string name="match">Tomar Servicio</string>
    <string name="seguir_buscando">Seguir Buscando</string>
    <string name="basico1">Básico 1</string>
    <string name="basico2">Básico 2</string>
    <string name="basico3">Básico 3</string>
    <string name="basico4">Básico 4</string>
    <string name="basico5">Básico 5</string>
    <string name="Inermedio1">Intermedio 1</string>
    <string name="Intermedio1">Intermedio 1</string>
    <string name="intermedio2">Intermedio 2</string>
    <string name="intermedio3">Intermedio 3</string>
    <string name="intermedio4">Intermedio 4</string>
    <string name="intermedio5">Intermedio 5</string>
    <string name="avanzado1">Avanzado 1</string>
    <string name="avanzado2">Avanzado 2</string>
    <string name="avanzado3">Avanzado 3</string>
    <string name="avanzado4">Avanzado 4</string>
    <string name="avanzado5">Avanzado 5</string>
    <string name="seccion1">I. Collocate the words in their correct order to form coherent sentences in Present simple To be and Present simple Do.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico2">II. Underline the correct option to create sentences in Present progressive.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico3">" III. Underline the correct comparative or superlative adjective."</string>
    <string name="diagnostico4">IV. Select the correct option used to or didn’t use to.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico5">V. Match the sentences 26-30 with the phrases a-f. First conditional.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico6">VI. Match the sentences 31-35 with the phrases a-f. Second conditional.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico7">VII. Underline the correct verb to create coherent passive voice sentences.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico8">VIII. Write the verbs in parentheses in the correct form. Use infinitive – ing verb patterns.</string>
    <string name="preguntasEnLectura">I really needed 0. _____to go_____ (go) for a drink, I went to an Irish bar and there I met my girlfriend Laura, It was when I studied medicine in the 90’s, firstly, I approached elegantly 41. _______________ (invite) her a wine’s cup, later, I made some jokes because I desperately wanted 42. _______________ (get) her confidence and appear more natural, but, she didn’t smile, so, I asked her 43. _______________ (dance), it seems that I’m more agile with my feet than with the lips, she told me “I love 44. _______________ (do) Yoga”, Have you ever practiced it?,  I answered,  well,  I have  never done it,  but,  if  you  teach  me,  I  will enjoy    45. _______________ (be) your student, that’s for sure!, she laughed at my comment and that was the beginning of our relationship.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico9">IX.  Select the correct option to report every sentence. Reported speech.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico10">X. Select only T (true) or F (false) according to your comprehension.</string>
    <string name="preguntasEnLectura2">“The Rodriguez Brothers Circus”, the most famous one of California, is in town! Every year, the circus arrives and stays for a week, then they go to the next town. It used to have a lot of animals, but now there are not many, before, people used to like seeing animals performing, however, times have changed. There is still an elephant which is called Jacob and two old lions, Hattie and Meg. Most of the performers are human! There is Leopold, “The Strongest Man in the World”, it is known by co-workers that his father also worked in the circus, but Leopold is stronger than him, he has bigger arms and bigger legs too! Leopold performs his act every night for the town’s people who come to watch, another performer is Clara, she has the longest hair in the world, it’s about 4 meters long! She also has a daughter who works in the circus, her name is Sue-Ellen. Her hair is a lot shorter, but she wants to grow it as long as her mother’s, Sue-Ellen has helped to look after the animals since she was five years old. The highlight of the circus are the three clowns, Pit, Pot and Pat, they have always worn long red shoes, but Pat’s shoes are the longest and sometimes, he falls over because they’re so long! They perform for about twenty minutes and they are always the most popular act with the audience, especially the children. For many years was thought that Pit, Pot and Pat were brothers, but Pat is older than the other two – now it is publicly known that he’s their father! He’s the oldest clown in the country, but he has a lot of energy. Tomorrow will be the longest day because the circus is leaving town and everything must be packed away into big trucks.</string>
    <string name="diagnostico11">XI. Read very carefully the extract and answer the next questions.</string>
    <string name="texto1">Nanorobotics is the emerging technology field creating machines or robots whose components are at or close to the scale of a nanometer (10−9 meters).More specifically, nanorobotics refers to the nanotechnology engineering discipline of designing and building nanorobots, with devices ranging in size from 0.1–10 micrometers and constructed of nanoscale or molecular components.The names nanobots, nanoids, nanites, nanomachines or nanomites have also been used to describe these devices currently under research and development.\nAnother definition is a robot that allows precision interactions with nanoscale objects, or can manipulate with nanoscale resolution. Such devices are more related to microscopy or scanning probe microscopy, instead of the description of nanorobots as molecular machine. Following the microscopy definition even a large apparatus such as an atomic force microscope can be considered a nanorobotic instrument when configured to perform nanomanipulation. For this perspective, macroscale robots or microrobots that can move with nanoscale precision can also be considered nanorobots. Nanomachines are largely in the research-and-development phase, but some primitive molecular machines have been tested. An example is a sensor having a switch approximately 1.5 nanometers across, capable of counting specific molecules in a chemical sample. The first useful applications of nanomachines might be in medical technology, which could be used to identify and destroy cancer cells.</string>
    <string name="texto2">Nubot is an abbreviation for \"nucleic acid robot.\" Nubots are organic molecular machines at the nanoscale. DNA structure can provide means to assemble 2D and 3D nanomechanical devices. DNA based machines can be activated using small molecules, proteins and other molecules of DNA. Biological circuit gates based on DNA materials have been engineered as molecular machines to allow in-vitro drug delivery for targeted health problems. Such material based systems would work most closely to smart biomaterial drug system delivery.</string>
    <string name="texto3">This approach proposes the use of biological microorganisms, like the bacterium Escherichia coli. Thus the model uses a flagellum for propulsion purposes. Electromagnetic fields normally control the motion of this kind of biological integrated device.</string>

</resources>
